Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Press Office: Speeches (Accession 38997, 39744 and 40172), 1998-2002., Extent: 8.5 cu. ft. (Box 9, 78-85)
  - State Council of Higher Education Board of Visitors Training Program, 1998 August (Box 78, Folder 93)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission on Higher Education, 1998 August 25 (Box 78, Folder 94)
  - Lorton Prison, 1998 August 26 (Box 78, Folder 95)
  - Council on Technology Services (COTS), 1998 August 27 (Box 78, Folder 96)
  - Speech Log, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 97)
  - Information Technology Showcase, 1998 January 9 (Box 78, Folder 98)
  - Mike Hardy Interview on the Mental Health System, 1998 September 2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Hopewell Award, 1998 September 8 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Agency Head meeting, 1998 September 9 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Wallops Island Announcement, 1998 September 14 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Day on Capitol Hill, 1998 September 15 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Children First Education Initiative, 1998 September 18 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Retreat at The Tides Inn, 1998 September 18 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Commission on Information Technology, 1998 September 22 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Small Business Innovation Research Awards Ceremony, 1998 September 23 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - State Employee Town Hall Meetings, 1998 September 23-25 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - National Rifle Association (NRA), 1998 September 27 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Council, 1998 September 28 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Pre-paid Education Program Press Conference, 1998 October 1 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Rededication of Lee Chapel, 1998 October 3 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - SEUS/Japan Joint Meeting, 1998 October 5 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Exile: Project Exile for the Commonwealth, 1998 October 6 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Hewlett-Packard Economic Development, 1998 October 8 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Combined Virginia Campaign, 1998 October 8 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Adjutant General Claude Williams, 1998 October 14 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - VDOT Conference at VMI, 1998 October 15 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Prevent Blindness Awards Dinner, 1998 October 15 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Annual Campaign Breakfast with Tom Bliley, 1998 October 19 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Larry Sabato Roast, 1998 October 20 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Real Estate Luncheon, 1998 October 20 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Senator Stephen Martin Reception, 1998 October 22 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Fall Forum on Crime, 1998 October 21 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - South Carolina Car Tax News Conference, 1998 October 26 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Delegate Dick Black Reception, 1998 October 26 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Delegate Devolites Reception, 1998 October 27 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Yvonne Smith Party Conversion, 1998 October 27 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Bob Vila/Roxane Gilmore, 1998 October 28 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Prince William 66 Partnership Reception, 1998 October 28 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Bristol Compressor, 1998 October 30 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Joe Barta Campaign Tour, 1998 October 30 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Amendments 3 and 4 Rally, Northern Virginia, 1998 November 2 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Ellen Sauerbrey Tour, 1998 November 1 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Senator Martin Williams Reception, 1998 November 4 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - French Ambassador Luncheon, 1998 November 5 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Oracle Corporation, 1998 November 6 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Business Council, 1998 November 6 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - GOPac Annual Meeting, 1998 November 8 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Senator Fred Quayle Reception, 1998 November 9 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - SEUS/Korea Reception, 1998 November 7 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - New Majority Pac, 1998 November 10 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Veterans Day Speech, 1998 November 11 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - NAACP Annual Convention, 1998 November 12 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Centenarians Celebration, 1998 November 13 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - National Rifle Association (NRA) Museum Dedication, 1998 November 16 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 1998 November 16 (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - The Virginia Promise, 1998 November 17 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Report to Top Management, 1998 November 19 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - American Council on Germany Breakfast, 1998 November 19 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - Reception and Dinner for Delegate JoAnn Davis, 1998 November 23 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - MCI Worldcom Announcement, 1998 November 24 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - Lunch for Delegate Vince Callahan, 1998 November 27 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - Governor's Commission on Information Technology, 1998 December 2 (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - Family Foundation Gala, 1998 December 3 (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - Republican Advance, Chantilly, 1998 December 5 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - Reception for Delegate Michele McQuigg, 1998 December 6 (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - Water Quality Improvement, 1998 December 7 (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - Reception for Delegate Allen Dudley, 1998 December 8 (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - Virginia Strategy, 1998 December 9 (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - RPV Roundtable Luncheon, 1998 December 10 (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - Tourism Announcement, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission on Higher Education, 1998 December 10 (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - Virginia Strategy, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - Wytheville Economic Development Announcement, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - Roger Rife Endorsment, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - Rural Economic Development Announcement in Abingdon, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - Rural Economic Development Announcement in Danville, 1998 December 11 (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - George Mason University Announcements, 1998 December 13 (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - Old Dominion University Announcements, 1998 December 13 (Box 79, Folder 72)
  - Roanoke Higher Education Center Announcements, 1998 December 13 (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - Delegate Eric Cantor Breakfast, 1998 December 15 (Box 79, Folder 74)
  - Mental Health Budget Announcement, 1998 December 16 (Box 79, Folder 75)
  - State Employee Budget Announcement, 1998 December 17 (Box 79, Folder 76)
  - Amendments to the 1998-2000 Biennial Budget, 1998 December 18 (Box 79, Folder 77)
  - Black Universities Announcement, 1998 December 15 (Box 79, Folder 78)
  - Fredericksburg Tourism Announcement, 1998 December 21 (Box 79, Folder 79)
  - Henrico Business Council, 1999 January 6 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Virginia's School Performance Report Card, 1999 January 6 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Council Reception, 1999 January 7 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Las Vegas Convenction Center, 1999 Janurary 8 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address, 1999 January 9 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Federation of Republican Women, 1999 January 13 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Opening of Sussex II, 1999 January 18 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health Inspector General Appointment, 1999 January 19 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson Institute Reception, 1999 january 19 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Y2K Summit for Local Government, 1999 January 22 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference, 1999 January 23 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Journal Newspapers Business Luncheon, 1999 January 26 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Police Rally, 1999 January 27 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Energy Recovery, 1999 January 29 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Government Performance Project, 1999 February 1 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - State Terrorism Policy Summit, 1999 February 2 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Eternal Technology, 1999 February 4 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Gateway Computers, 1999 February 5 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Capital One, 1999 February 9 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - CIT Board Meeting, 1999 February 10 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Fifth Annual Tribute Dinner, 1999 February 11 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Elaine McConnell Birthday Party, 1999 February 12 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Out of State Waste Press Conference, 1999 February 11 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Celebration, 1999 February 15 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - RGA Gala Dinner, 1999 Februrary 22 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - A.T. Massey Safety Dinner, 1999 February 25 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Sine Die Speech, 1999 February 27 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Washington Post Rededication, 1999 March 1 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - HP Hood Announcement, 1999 March 4 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - VASHIC Groundbreaking, 1999 March 9 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - AOL Expansion Announcement, 1999 March 10 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Pi Phi Alpha, 1999 March 12 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - William Fralin Announcement, 1999 March 18 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1999 March 19 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - WRVA "Ask Governor Gilmore", 1999 March 25 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Internet Policy Act Signing, 1999 March 30 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - NY Stock Exchange Board of Directors, 1999 April 1 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Terrorism Adviory Panel, 1999 April 6 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Sheriff Carl R. Peed Campaign Kick-off, 1999 April 8 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Terry G. Kilgore Fundraiser, 1999 April 9 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Opening of Wallens Ridge State Prison, 1999 April 9 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Mark Earley Fundraiser, 1999 April 10 (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Allen for Senate Announcement, 1999 April 13 (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - IEEE Cement Industry, Roanoke, 1999 April 13 (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Burton Committee, 1999 Aoril 14 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - A New Type of Tax Cut Movement, 1999 April 14 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Republican Radio Response, 1999 April 3 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - Endorsement of George W. Bush for President, 1999 April 16 (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - 79th Annual Maritime Banquet, 1999 April 22 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Emmett Hanger Lunch, 1999 April 26 (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - Virginia Women's Institute for Leadership, 1999 April 26 (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - Ed-Flex, 1999 April 26 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - WTOP, DC Call-in show, 1999 April 27 (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - RNC Gala, 1999 April 28 (Box 80, Folder 54)
  - State Council of Higher Education in Virginia (SCHEV) - Board of Visitors, 1999 April 30 (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - Ruble Hord Endorsement, 1999 May 3 (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - Henrico County Circuit Court Judges, 1999 May 4 (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - Partnership for School Safety, 1999 May 10 (Box 80, Folder 58)
  - Governor's Commission on Information Technology, 1999 May 12 (Box 80, Folder 59)
  - Delegate Kathy Byron, 1999 May 12 (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) Commencement, 1999 May 15 (Box 80, Folder 61)
  - Virginia State University (VSU) Commencement, 1999 May 16 (Box 80, Folder 62)
  - Business Appreciation Breakfast, 1999 May 17 (Box 80, Folder 63)
  - Fundraiser for George Broman in Culpeper, 1999 May 17 (Box 80, Folder 64)
  - Culpeper's 250th Anniversary Celebration, 1999 May 17 (Box 80, Folder 65)
  - Fundraiser for Buck Waters in Manassas, 1999 May 18 (Box 80, Folder 66)
  - Governor's Commission on Transportation Policy, 1999 May 19 (Box 80, Folder 67)
  - Tobacco Growers Association Annual Meeting, 1999 Feburary 13 (Box 80, Folder 68)
  - Speech log, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 69)
  - Small Business Administration Awards Luncheon, 1999 June 11 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - National Taxpayers' Union Luncheon, 1999 June 12 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Siemens Expansion Event, 1999 June 15 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Republican Party Fundraiser, 1999 June 15 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Mel Sheridan, 1999 June 6 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - National Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce, 1999 June 22 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Pharming Healthcare Announcement, 1999 June 29 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Commission on Transportation Policy, 1999 June 29 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Del. Roger McClure Fundraising Luncheon, 1999 June 30 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Volvo Groundbreaking, 1999 July 1 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Institute for Forensic Science and Medicine, 1999 July 2 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Naturalization Ceremony at Monticello, 1999 July 4 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Weekly column on Y2K bug, 1999 July 12 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - George Bush Fundraising Luncheon, 1999 July 14 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Conference on Education, 1999 July 20 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Kraft Plant in Winchester, 1999 July 29 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Conference of Chief Justices and State Court Administrators, 1999 August 3 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Exile, 1999 August 6 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Tobacco Trust Certification Board, 1999 August 17 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Del. Frank Ruff Roundtable and Dinner, 1999 August 18 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Dept. of Transportation Environmental Mishaps News Conference, 1999 August 19 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Nick Rerras Fundraiser, 1999 August 23 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Remarks to Senate Finance Committee, 1999 August 23 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Transportation in Virginia, 1999 August 31 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Information Technology at George Mason University, 1999 Septemmber 1 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Hurricane Floyd news conference, 1999 September 15 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - John Alderman Installation, 1999 September 20 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - A.V. Buck Madra for Supervisor reception, 1999 September 20 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Sabre Project Announcement, 1999 September 20 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Nick Rerras dinner, 1999 September 23 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Right Choices for Youth, 1999 September 23 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Utility Economic Development Announcement, 1999 September 27 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Commonwealth Council meeting, 2000 January 6 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - CES Internet Summit, 2000 January 7 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address, 2000 January 12 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - RNC Eagles Luncheon in Palm Springs, CA, 2000 January 15 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - L. Douglas Wilder Dinner, 2000 January 20 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Political Action Conference, 2000 January 21 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Ongoing winter weather event, 2000 January 27 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Dulles Corridor Rail Association Reception, 2000 January 31 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Republican Legislative Campaign Fund, 2000 February 2 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission on Higher Education, 2000 February 3 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly meeting at Colonial Capitol Building, 2000 February 5 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Bush introduction, 2000 February 9 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Wake County GOP President's Day Dinner in Raleigh, 2000 February 11 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Indian CEO High Tech Council, 2000 February 15 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Regional Terrorism Policy Forum in Atlanta, 2000 Februay 17 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Black History Month Reception, 2000 February 21 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Southside Economic Development Announcement, 2000 February 22 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Associate Industries of Massachusettes, 2000 February 23 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Youth Leadership Initiative Dinner, 2000 February 24 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Republican Party of Virginia Gala, 2000 February 25 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Governor Bush intoduction in Newport News, 2000 February 25 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Bush Virginia Primary celebration, 2000 February 29 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - SCHEV Faculty Awards, 2000 March 2 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - BI Chemicals Economic Development announcemnt, 2000 March 9 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Celebration of Words, 2000 March 11 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Global Cabinet Summit at George Mason Univerity, 2000 March 13 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - UCITA bill signing, 2000 March 14 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Senator Ed Schrock Announcement for Congress, 2000 March 23 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak in Tyson's Corner, 2000 March 27 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - NOVA Urban League, 2000 March 31 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Investiture Ceremony for Donald W. Lemmons, 2000 April 4 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Telecommunications, Trade and Consumer Protection Subcommittee of the Commerce Commission, 2000 April 6 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Project Exile, House Resolution 4051, Washington DC, 2000 April 6 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Model General Assembly, 2000 April 7 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Mark Earley dinner, 2000 April 7 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - ABCNews.com interview, 2000 April 7 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Commonwealth Council luncheon, 2000 April 13 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Nylstar announcement, 2000 April 14 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - 6th District Republican Committee dinner, 2000 April 14 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Nationwide Homes Economic Development announcement, 2000 April 14 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Philip Morris Annual Meeting dinner, 2000 April 26 (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Northern Virginia Technology Council, 2000 April 25 (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - GE Annual Meeting, 2000 April 25 (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Grocery Manufacturers of America Governor's Forum, 2000 April 25 (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Oklahoma State Republican Party Convention, 2000 April 29 (Box 82, Folder 45)
  - Tourism Conference, 2000 May 1 (Box 82, Folder 46)
  - Litton PRC, 2000 May 2 (Box 82, Folder 47)
  - Dominion Short Pump Opening, 2000 May 5 (Box 82, Folder 48)
  - Dominion Semi-conductor Economic Development announcement, 2000 May 9 (Box 82, Folder 49)
  - Business Council, 2000 May 11 (Box 82, Folder 50)
  - Introduction of the President of Ireland, 2000 May 15 (Box 82, Folder 51)
  - Delaware Republican Party, 2000 May 19 (Box 82, Folder 52)
  - Annual meeting of State Agency Leaders, 2000 May 24 (Box 82, Folder 53)
  - AOL Ribbon Cutting, 2000 May 25 (Box 82, Folder 54)
  - RNC Gore-itis, 2000 May 26 (Box 82, Folder 55)
  - RPV State Convention in Virginia Beach, 2000 June 3 (Box 82, Folder 56)
  - World Congress on Information Technology, 2000 June 13 (Box 82, Folder 57)
  - Girls State, 2000 June 20 (Box 82, Folder 58)
  - RGA/Education Facts, 2000 June 26 (Box 82, Folder 59)
  - Commonwealth Council - Education, 2000 June 28 (Box 82, Folder 60)
  - National Conservative 4th of July Soiree, 2000 July 4 (Box 82, Folder 61)
  - Jefferson Literary and Debating Society, 2000 July 15 (Box 82, Folder 62)
  - Republican National Convention in Philadelphia, 2000 August 2 (Box 82, Folder 63)
  - Year of Record Economic Performance, 2000 August 21 (Box 82, Folder 64)
  - Global Center announcement, 2000 August 23 (Box 82, Folder 65)
  - Mays and Valentine briefing, 2000 August 24 (Box 82, Folder 66)
  - Commission on Information Technology - Digital Dominion, 2000 August 31 (Box 82, Folder 67)
  - Speech log, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 68)
  - Oklahoma State Republican Party, 2000 April 29 (Box 82, Folder 69)
  - Ehrlich for Congress Luncheon Fundraiser2000 September 6 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - AOL@School and PowerUp, 2000 September 6 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Agency Heads meeting, 2000 September 7 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - SOL test results news conference, 2000 September 7 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - President George H. W. Bush introduction, 2000 September 8 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Tidewater Elementary School, 2000 September 8 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Tredegar National Civil War Center announcement, 2000 September 12 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Southern States Energy Board meeting in Memphis, TN, 2000 September 13 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Transportation Commission's 2nd Interim Report, 2000 September 14 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Eric Cantor breakfast, 2000 September 18 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Education Conference, 2000 September 19 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Right Choices for Youth conference, 2000 September 18 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Victory 2000 team meeting, 2000 September 16 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Car tax news conference, 2000 September 2000 16 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Institute luncheon2000 September 22 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Cecil Underwood Media availability and luncheon, 2000 September 16 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - COVITS 2000 Information Technology Symposium, 2000 September 27 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Patrick Henry College, 2000 September 30 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Campaign tour for Richard Vinroot, Candidate for Governor of North Carolina, Raleigh, 2000 October 4 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Campaign tour for Jim Talent, Candidate for Governor of Missouri, 2000 October 9 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Capital One economic development announcement, 2000 October 10 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - HP Hood facility opening, 2000 October 11 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - RGA Media availability, 2000 October 13 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Quarter lunch, 2000 October 16 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - eVenture World Summit dinner remarks, 2000 October 15 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - eVenture World Summit opening remarks, 2000 October 16 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - President's Cup opening ceremonies, 2000 October 17 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Main Street Station restoration, 2000 October 17 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Victory 2000/Kentucky and South Carolina, 2000 October 19 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - VMI Campaign kickoff dinner, 2000 October 21 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Statewide success on the SOLs, 2000 October 24 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Academic Challenge announcement, 2000 October 26 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Allen 2000 Campaign, 2000 October 27 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Allen for Senate news conference, 2000 November 3 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Reagan National Airport news conference, 2000 November 6 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Report to Top Management, New York City, 2000 November 9 (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Charlottesville Chamber of Commerce, 2000 November 13 (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Florida's law on results to be certified, 2000 November 14 (Box 83, Folder 38)
  - Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2000 November 22 (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - William Styron tribute, 2000 December 1 (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Free Congress Foundation, Washington, DC, 2000 December 4 (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - K-12 education amendments to the budget, 2000 December 7 (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - USS Wisconsin, 2000 December 7 (Box 83, Folder 43)
  - 17th Annual Republican Advance, 2000 December 8 (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Governor's Commission on Transportation Policy, 2000 December 11 (Box 83, Folder 45)
  - Press conference on transportation reform, 2000 December 13 (Box 83, Folder 46)
  - Terrorism Conference, National Press Club, 2000 December 14 (Box 83, Folder 47)
  - Higher Education budget announcement, 2000 December 15 (Box 83, Folder 48)
  - Car Tax, 2000 December 18 (Box 83, Folder 49)
  - Virginia members of the Electoral College, 2000 December 18 (Box 83, Folder 50)
  - Governor's 2000-2002 biennial budget amendments, 2000 December 20 (Box 83, Folder 51)
  - RNC nomination as chairman, 2000 December 22 (Box 83, Folder 52)
  - Commonwealth Council, 2001 January 4 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address, 2001 January 10 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Virtual visitor center, 2001 January 12 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Celebration, 2001 January 15 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Fraternal Order of Police, 2001 January 24 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - WRVA radio, 2001 January 31 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Republican Congressional Leadership Retreat, 2001 February 2 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Meet the Press, 2001 February 4 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Association of School Business Officials, 2001 February 8 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Promotion of Colonel Burt Holmes, Jr., 2001 February 14 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Conservative Political Action Committee, 2001 February 15 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Missouri Republican Party Lincoln Day Dinner, 2001 February 17 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Car Tax, 2001 February 21 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Budget News Conference, 2001 February 24 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - President of Columbia, 2001 February 25 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Budget News Conference II, 2001 February 26 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - RNC Black History Month, 2001 February 28 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - S.C. Silver Elephant Banquet, 2001 March 2 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - USS Ronald Reagan christening, 2001 March 4 (Box 84, Folder 19)